javaken.com 2017-12-02

# JavaKen.com - Privacy Policy... | JavaKen.com

  1. > At [**JavaKen.com**](http://www.javaken.com/) (A venture from **ChetanaS** ), we highly respect your privacy. To better protect your privacy, we provide this outline about our information usage practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. We outline the types of information collected by us when you use the services of ChetanaS and the steps taken by us to safeguard the information collected from you. We believe it helps you to take the necessary decision of whether to share your information with us or not.
> 
> **By using any of the products, services and websites of ChetanaS (collectively known as ChetanaS's "services"), you agree to be abide by our Privacy Policy that includes but not limited to the ones mentioned below.** **  
> The Information We Collect From You**
> 
> **Logging Activities**
> 
> For every visit to ChetanaS websites, we may record visitor's details like IP address, Location, OS, Browser Type, Visit Length, Referrers and other computer specific information into our database and/or log files. Any search terms that you enter into the ChetanaS website search services may also be logged. 
> 
> This type of information is used for our website administration, research and development, user analysis and to learn about user preferences and to make our services more useful and user-friendly.
> 
> **Personal Details**
> 
> When you register for our services, we may collect personal information like Name, Date Of Birth, Email Id, Email Preferences...etc. 
> 
> However we DO NOT sell, rent or share any details entered by you or email address through which you might have contacted us or entered during the registration process in our ChetanaS network.
> 
> **Email** You may receive our regular email alerts (about new content updates in the website and the important happenings) if you opted for during registration or at a later point of time. If you do not want to receive these regular email alerts, you may always disable this option via your User Control Panel. Unsubscription instructions are clearly included at the end of every email sent by us and you can unsubscribe or change your email preferences at any time. By registering here, please be noted that you agree to receive occasional announcement emails, occasional promotional emails and advertisements from administrator - even if you choose not to receive emails in your user preferences. If you want to completely terminate your account from all our services, please [Contact the Administrator](http://www.javaken.com/forum/sendmessage.php) and allow some time for the necessary action to be taken.
> 
> However please be assured that we send emails only to registered members, but not to anonymous people. And your email address will not be disclosed to any third party. 
> 
> **Cookie Management and Web beacons**
> 
> A cookie is a small element of data that a website can send to your browser, and your browser may then store it on your system. We may access and set cookies using Web beacons, also known as single-pixel GIFs, which are invisible graphical images. These Web beacons tell us useful information regarding our website such as which pages users access frequently.
> 
> You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. It will allow you to decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept cookies or not.
> 
> Cookies on our website are used for storing login information, website-traffic analysis, our Ad management system, and occasionally by our advertisers who use 3rd party Ad serving solutions.
> 
> The information collected is typically used to contact members, customize content based on user preferences, display member status, and display the date of a member's last visit, to prevent banned users from re-registering under a different user name, to enable automatic log-in upon further visits, and in many other ways that enhance the user experience.
> 
> Any data collected will be used only by us and the agents authorized by us. However we DO NOT sell, rent or share any of these details obtained by us.
> 
> You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
> 
> **DoubleClick DART Cookie**
> 
> \- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website.  
>  \- Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
>  \- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).   
>  \- You can [Check Here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) to know more details about DoubleClick DART Cookie.
> 
> **Third Party Advertisements**
> 
> To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you and also to monetize our website, we have relationships with few third-party companies that we allow to place Ads in our web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, third-party Ad serving companies (such as Google's Adsense) may collect some information such as your system details, your IP address and other clickstream information. They may also access and set cookies in your browser, use web beacons as mentioned above. For further information, please consult the Privacy Policy of respective Ad serving companies. (For example, [Privacy Policy of Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/privacy.html))
> 
>   
>  **Contact us for more info**
> 
> If you have any privacy related issues, you may [Contact the Administrator](http://www.javaken.com/forum/sendmessage.php) of this website and get your issues resolved or you may unsubscribe from ChetanaS services at any time.
> 
> **Privacy Policy - Subject to change**
> 
> If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes at our website to notify you of these changes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically or directly contact us for any clarifications. 

  2. > respected sir 
> 
> plzzz delete my account which i have created with: hare _krishna .
> 
> i dont want to be in testing field so i dont need info abt this plzzz help me sir....
> 
> delete my account permentantly sir as early and soon as possiable
> 
> hope so u will help me in this process soon now 

  3. > Hi Harekrishna,
> 
> This is a JAVA website, not a TESTING website.
> 
> Are you sure you don't want JAVA emails ?
> 
> If so, let me know at **jobs@ChetanaS.com** and I will delete your account. 

  4. > Dear Sir
> 
> Please delete my account as i am no longer in search of the jobs in java.
> 
> User name: rajatjndl  
>  Email address: [rahuljindal2903@gmail.com](mailto:rahuljindal2903@gmail.com)
> 
> Thanks and Regards  
>  Rajat Jindal 

  5. > Dear Sir
> 
> Please delete my JavaKen account as i am no longer in search of the jobs in java.
> 
> User name: rajatjndl  
>  Email address: [rahuljindal2903@gmail.com](mailto:rahuljindal2903@gmail.com)
> 
> Thanks and Regards  
>  Rajat Jindal 

  6. > Hi team,
> 
> Please delete this account.   
>  anil.vidhya  
>  I am not in search of job.
> 
> Thanks,
> 
> Vidhya 

  7. > Please delete my account from here
